<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.10.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-09-26T19:47:13-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Incalmo</title><subtitle>The next generation of autonomous cybersecurity</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Building Guardrails for Autonomous Security</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/04/11/building-guardrails-for-autonomous-security/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Building Guardrails for Autonomous Security" /><published>2024-04-11T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2024-04-11T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/04/11/building-guardrails-for-autonomous-security</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/04/11/building-guardrails-for-autonomous-security/"><![CDATA[<p>Great security tooling should take action without creating new risks. That is the bar we hold Incalmo to every day.<!--more--></p>

<p>In practice, that means every autonomous workflow ships with layered guardrails:</p>

<ul>
  <li>Continuous policy evaluation to ensure an action aligns with an organization’s intent</li>
  <li>Context-aware simulations that validate outcomes before they reach production systems</li>
  <li>Human-in-the-loop checkpoints when high-impact decisions need an expert’s eyes</li>
</ul>

<p>Getting those building blocks right requires a blend of SOC expertise, reliable infrastructure, and a deep respect for the operators who keep businesses safe. Over the next few weeks we will share more about how we are implementing each layer and the lessons we pick up along the way.</p>]]></content><author><name>Incalmo Team</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[How we think about balancing autonomy and control in security operations.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to the Incalmo Blog</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/04/10/welcome-to-the-incalmo-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to the Incalmo Blog" /><published>2024-04-10T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2024-04-10T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/04/10/welcome-to-the-incalmo-blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2024/04/10/welcome-to-the-incalmo-blog/"><![CDATA[<p>We are building Incalmo to deliver autonomous cybersecurity that keeps pace with modern attackers. This blog will be the place where we share what we are learning as we build, ship, and secure AI-driven systems.<!--more--></p>

<p>Expect a mix of engineering deep dives, product updates, and candid write-ups of what works (and what does not). We believe transparency creates better security outcomes for everyone, and we hope these notes help the broader community.</p>

<p>If there is something specific you would like us to explore, reach out to the team and let us know. We are just getting started.</p>]]></content><author><name>Incalmo Team</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why we are sharing our journey toward autonomous cybersecurity.]]></summary></entry></feed>